Fadel Muhammad

Full Stack Developer

About

I am learning about programing more than 3 years. I am a fast learner and , I am ready for learn about new programing language on my current company I am developing 2 project using Laravel and 2 Apps using Java Spring boot and more than what I wrote here I developing much much apps for my client. with good team and I provide every datas on database SQL/Non-SQL for mobile developer (API) and fixing some bug using Javascruot, Spring, Php on my job.

Education

Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika

Associate of Computer - System Information, 2017 - 2020

Experiences

PT Mitra Transaksi Indonesia

Jan 2022 - Present

- Developing PWA QRIS Mandiri (Livin Usaha) using React is and Spring (On Client)
- Developing Nyala By OCBC
- Developing Training Website Apps
- Handle fixing and bugs
- Add Features and creating document project

PT Rekayasa Aplikasi Digital

Oct 2020 - Dec 2021

Full-Stack Developer

- Lead Of Project Sekolahdigi & Bantubeli
- Developing Apps & Website Bantubeli using Laravel
- Developing Apps & Website Sekolahdigi using Laravel
- Coordinating across teams (Mobile and Front-End)
- Integration Payment Gateway
- Integration Shipping Delivery Service on Bantubeli
- Helping team on fixing some bugs

PT Sahabat Sejahtera

Jan 2019 - Oct 2020

Full-Stack Developer

- Developing website catalog using Codelgniter
- Management all product on website

Skills

Spring Boot

Javascript Framework

Laravel

SQL (Oracle, MySQL)

Non-SQL (Firebase)

Have knowledge about creating

REST API

Have knowledge data structures

Familiar using Git

Languages

English: Written.

Indonesia: Spoken, Written.

Contact

Email: fadel.mm01@gmail.com
Linkedin: Fadel Muhammad

Telp: 081290669170

Github: sipadl Instagram: si.padl